Guide to the Radio Haiti Audio Recordings, 1957-2003 RL.10059
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General Programming
  - AJH, reyaksyon rapò ankèt sou lanmò Jean Dominique, 2003-01-29 (Box RR042, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1163)
  - Rapport enquête Parquet Publication, 2003-01-29 (Box RR042, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1139)
  - Dwa moun reyaction Jn Do., 2003-01-30 (Box RR042, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1140)
  - Droits Humains réaction., 2003-01-30 (Box RR042, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1141)
  - AJH, Michèle Montas, 2003-02-05 (Box RR042, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1151)
  - Aristide, trafik dwòg, Etazini, 2003-02-05 (Box RR042, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1164)
  - Arestasyon jij Agnant, 2003-02-10 (Box RR042, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1153)
  - Jistis, dosye Agnant, 2003-02-12 (Box RR042, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1159)
  - Aristide, kriz politik, OEA ak KARIKOM, 2003-02-16 (Box RR042, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1154)
  - Vyolans Site Solèy, 2003-02-18 (Box RR042, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1160)
  - Kidnapin meri Petyonvil, 2003-02-18 (Box RR042, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1161)
  - Déclaration de Michèle Montas sur radio sœur, 2003-04-02 (Box CS051, Audio-cassette RL10059-CS-1860)
  - Message de Michèle Montas à l'occasion de la remise du Prix Jean Léopold Dominique, 2003-05 (Box CS048, Audio-cassette RL10059-CS-1769)
  - Archive 1970-72 (1), undated (Box CS027, Audio-cassette RL10059-DAT-0003)
  - Archive 72-73 (2), undated (Box CS027, Audio-cassette RL10059-DAT-0004)
  - Zafè Jean Dominique, jen 2001, undated (Box RR037, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-0996)
  - Mizik pou Jando: Zaka Ginen, Boukman Eksperyans, Haiti Rap Fòs, Samba Zao, undated (Box CS054, Audio-cassette RL10059-CS-1952)
  - Spot Radyo Ayiti, undated (Box CS028, Audio-cassette RL10059-DAT-0001)
  - Le marchand de surettes, Jean L. Dominique, undated (Box RR017, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-0496)
  - Radyo Ayiti se yon lekòl, undated (Box RR116, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1655)
  - Virgules: IA, undated (Box CS053, Audio-cassette RL10059-CS-1924)
  - Radio Haiti musiques originals: Restez toujours branchés (ça cayes[??]); Sur Haïti Inter I/A tout pour vous satisfaire (chwal la pa malen); 1330 sur le cadran (Damballa nou ??); Du lundi au samedi (Feuille nan bois, Ti zan Do); A toutes les heures, actualités; Vous captez RHI (Ti Zoiseau); Bonjour à tous (Reine Soleil); Haïti Inter AM/FM (Damballah Ouedo); Variétés qui fait plaisir (Loco de la mente); Voux captez H. Inter (Minis Azaka, Bonsoir Dame); 1330 sur le cadran (Ibo Lélé), undated (Box RR116, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1653)
  - Poésies divers, Lobo, undated (Box RR119, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1679)
  - Side 1:. Side 2: Gary Victor, Sonson Pipirit: profil dʼun homme du peuple, undated (Box CS026, Audio-cassette RL10059-CS-0941)
  - Side 1:. Side 2: Diskou Aristide, undated (Box CS048, Audio-cassette RL10059-CS-1771)
  - Spot Haïti Inter, Thème Radio Haïti. Serenidad. Musiciens: Fritz St. Fleur (guitare, compositeur), Elifète Myrthil (clarinette, compositeur), Simeon Francique (violon), Amérique Fleurville (tambour, violon), Annette St Jean (soliste), Sonide Dupont (soliste), Renauld Marcelus (chanteur), Ronald Montes (bateur). Société Haïtienne d'aide aux aveugles (??), undated (Box RR116, Audio-reel RL10059-RR-1656)
- Additions
  - Accession 2021-0018
    - Wilfred "Tido" Lavaud interviews Frisner Augustin, Lois Wilcken, and Wendy Weisman for Radio Haiti Inter, Port-au-Prince, 12 August 1997 (Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository, Audio-file RL10059-WAV-0001_01.wav)
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      Tape loaned by Lois Wilcken for digitization, February 2021.
- Original tape boxes
  - Open reel tape boxes
    Scope and Contents
    Following digitization, the quarter-inch audio tapes in the Radio Haiti collection were spooled to new reels, which were then put in new tape boxes. The original tape boxes were kept for their potential descriptive (although much of this was captured during the pre-digitization phase of description) and technical informational value. The original tape boxes are contained in boxes RR059-RR115 and RR121-RR123. Contact Research Services staff for further information regarding accessing specific original tape boxes.